Hey, so this isn't matching up with this, and I'm not sure which one's right
Can you just hunt down the original part. Yes me do all right?
Hey Kev, what were you saying before about the paperwork? Me do now.
Go stop worry
Kevin do you feel okay? Me feel good body strong sleep big last night. Yeah, I think we should get him to the hospital.
Yeah, all right Kevin, why don't you come with us. No no. He's fine, he's fine. He's always been like that.
No he hasn't. I mean he's gotten worse over the years. He's making a statement
it's an ironic comment on our expectations of him, a funhouse image of our model of Kevin. you keep think that
Me mechanic not speak English, but he know what me mean when me say car no go
And we best friend so me think why waste time say lot word when few word do trick?
Kevin, I appreciate what you're trying to do.
Thank.
Here we have a word code the same way we have a dress code and what we're talking about is
Basically the speech equivalent to just wearing underpants
Sometimes words, you no need use
but need need for talk talk
But save time. more success.
Does it save time though? Cause we've been here for about an hour.
No me fault
Kevin at most you're saving a microscopic amount of time
Many small time make big time.
What are you gonna do with all this time?
See world.
Kevin you can't possibly save enough time to see the world.
Kevin, are you saying 'see the world' or 'Seaworld'?
Seaworld
Oceans. Fish.  Jump. China.
No see right there - that's the problem with your method because I still don't know if you're saying Seaworld or see the world
And it's taking a lot of time to explain it
Fine fine, I'll talk normally.
When me president, they see.
They see